CJ
Beautiful things, beautiful people.
This is what it's all about.
If you think the world looks good, guess what?
It does.
The Arctic turn travels an average of 71,000 kilometers a year.
And though fish are not animals, they do have feeling.
So think about that the next time you take a shit in the sea.
I have no obligation to say I love you if you say you love me.
It's not my fault you love me.
It's not anybody's fault that love is the only thought and pain is the only feeling.
If you ask me that doesn't sound like such a bad situation.
Existence is innocent.
Please don't try to think otherwise.
I was so charged to the game and blame it on the DJ that fell asleep at the decks.
At this point I feel like I'm almost 100% pure angel.
My history starts right now and I'm sorry for being late again.
I just didn't know I had to be on time every single time.
I really did love you and I'm sorry that we couldn't make it work.
I wish you all the best in your life and I'm sorry for always trying to see the funny side.
It just made everything in my life easier.
People need to stop trying to be cool and they need to start trying to be hot.
As you remember, the enemy is your self posed as a question.
I don't know much about anything really but I do know how life makes me feel.
It makes me feel both dead and alive just not at the same time.
But you know what the weirdest part is?
Of all the onions in the world I like to spring onions the best.
They give me hope.
Everything I said was true, apart from that last part.
And although the head hurts,
the heart knows the truth.